Oh, bine ai revenit.
Oh, welcome home.
M-am întors!
I'm home!
I've only just come back myself.
Today's forecast was spot-on! We had the first tropical day of the year.
FIRST DAUGHTER
Miharu
Weather
Reporter
College Freshman
I'm home!
That smells great!
I made coffee, Miharu.
Of course, there's some for you, too.
SECOND DAUGHTER
Mizore
High School Senior
Welcome home, my prince!
I've just finished baking some cookies.
THIRD DAUGHTER
Haruka
High School Junior
Delicious!
I'm so happy!
Now go and wash your hands.
I'll make you a snack.
Ta-da!
City
PLACE
Girls'
Fashion
Competition!
HAPPY FASHION
st
nd
rd
Ta-da!
Check this out!
This is me!
They took some pictures of me when I was walking around town!
SEVENTH DAUGHTER
Rikka
Seventh Grade
That's amazing, Rikka. You look just like a real model. It's so cool!
EIGHTH DAUGHTER
Kosame
Sixth Grade
I heard that models get loads of fan letters from boys!
That's no good at all!
Men are repulsive.
NINTH DAUGHTER
Urara
Fifth Grade
Don't worry about it!
I've already decided that Onii-chan is the one for me!
He's still a man!
I told you before that I'd rather die than have a guy live with us!
You're still saying that?
Onii-chan is part of our family.
Oh, I know what it is!
You actually love him, don't you?
It's just that you always pick on the ones you like.
Urara, you're so adorable!
That's not it at all!
I just really truly...
hate guys!
I think I'd like to go read outside today.
Want to go out for a bit?
According to Miharu's forecast, the highest temperature will be 32 degrees Celsius.
It may be a little too hot for us.
TWELFTH DAUGHTER
Fubuki
Second Grade
If we stay in the shade though, the wind
should cool us and we'll probably be okay.
They do say that negative ions in
the air are good for your health.
Thank you, Fubuki.
THIRTEENTH DAUGHTER
Watayuki
First Grade
Wait right there!
Take this! The Red Cliff Attack taught by Kong Ming himself!
Halt, false witch!
Happy Lucky Honeymoon B-B-Beam!
Silence, all of you!
Guards, attack with cake if you have no bread!
TENTH DAUGHTER
Seika
Fourth Grade
ELEVENTH
DAUGHTER
Yuuna
Third Grade
FOURTEENTH DAUGHTER
Mari
Kindergarten
Senior Class
Brother, play with me.
I've been a good girl, so please pat me.
FIFTEENTH DAUGHTER
Mizuki
Kindergarten
Middle Class
SEVENTEENTH DAUGHTER
Nijiko
2 Years Old
I wanna play with Onii-chan, too!
Me too!
SIXTEENTH
DAUGHTER
Sakura
Kindergarten
Junior Class
EIGHTEENTH DAUGHTER
Sora
1 Year Old
Let's play, Onii-chan!
NINETEENTH DAUGHTER
Asahi
0 Years Old
Oh, you're awake, A-chan?
I'm home!
It's so hot today.
Ow...
What a welcome.
Sorry!
What do you think you're doing, Manservant?!
Quit staring at me, you idiot!
EIGHTH DAUGHTER
Tsurara
Eighth Grade
You aren't hurt, are you, Onii-chan?
FIFTH DAUGHTER
Hotaru
Ninth Grade
I'm fine.
Sorry.
I don't really mind. Don't worry about it.
We're family after all.
FOURTH DAUGHTER
Hikaru
High School
Sophomore
Y-Yeah.
This Manservant's not family!
I'm never going to accept him!
Oh dear. What's my cute little daughter saying?
Mom!
You can't get along even though you're siblings? It breaks my heart!
Theatrical
Agency
CEO
MOM
? Years Old
I know!
I was just thinking of getting our office to make a promotion video for all of you.
Why don't you be the cameraman?
If we all take a trip for the shoot, I'm sure
you'll all get closer to one another!
Okay? Let's do it!
Good!
Mom never listens once she's decided something.
Bear with her, 'kay?
Un to baby
Totally, baby
Ai datte baby
It's love, baby
Wakaru desho?
Don't you know?
Kudasai na purinsesu tiara
Give me a princess's tiara
Watashi ni kagayaite suki katte ni kira kira
Sparkle at me, sparkle however you like
Paradise 0 [Love]
Honki wo shitteru yo (onna no ko)
We know how to go all out (We girls do)
Nani mo shiranai ne (kimi no koto)
We don't know anything (about you)
Hontou no yasashisa wa tsuyoi koto jya naino
Real kindness isn't all about being strong
Ittewa kurenaiyo kimi wa zurui
You don't say it, it's not fair
Ichiban daisuki ga (Suki dayo)
I want to see (I love you)
Onegai mitaino
who you love most, please
Maarui sekai kuru kuru shichau
The round world spins around
Kin iro no taiyou kisu wa taibou
A golden sun, an awaited kiss
Koi wa yakimochi de amaku meshiagare
Love is jealousy, have it nice and sweet
Marui no amai no baby saa motto tokkun shite
Round, sweet baby, work hard!
Kokoro wa dare no mono? (Watashi no mono jya nai)
Who owns that heart? (It isn't mine)
Dare no mono demo nai jiyuu damon
It isn't anyone's, because it's free
Tsubasa ga aru no kana kimagure oikakete
Does it have wings? Chase around it whimsically
Docchi ni icchaundarou ka?
Where is it going?
Daisoreta nozomi wo motteta
I had a wild wish
Nozomi kanaete tanoshikute mondai nai
Grant my wish. It's fun, so there's no problem
Gyutto baby
Squeeze me, baby
Ai nanda baby
It's love, baby
Wakatteyo
Understand this
Welcome
Yokubatte purinsesu tiara
Get a little greedy, princess tiara
Watashi mo kagayaiteru
I'm sparkling, too
Suki katte ni kira kira
Sparkling however I want to
You're so cool, Hikaru!
Look, Seika!
There's a lot of magical fish!
Lemme see!
Gotcha!
Why, you-!
It's cold!
Onii-chan!
Check out my swimsuit!
How is it?
My prince is looking at me in a swimsuit.
My heart won't stop pounding.
Huh? Why've you got a towel round you?
W-Well...
Amatsuka
Urara
What?! A school swimsuit?!
The other suits were all too flashy, so I couldn't pick one!
Oh? There's something on your butt.
A bug?
Wha- Get it off!
Get it off!
Oh no! What is it?!
What's on my butt?!
Are you all right, Onii-chan?!
What did you just do?!
What's going on?
There was something on Urara's swimsuit, so...
He touched my butt.
I'll never ever forgive you!
I'll call Mom up and go home!
I knew I couldn't go on a trip with a gu-
You've got a hole in your swimsuit.
You're right.
It's smaller than a spec of space dust.
I told you!
He found the hole.
Onii-chan, you're so kind!
Urara, maybe you're overthinking things.
You shouldn't worry about the swimsuit or the hole.
You were just embarrassed, right, Urara?
You needn't worry. It's fine.
Let's all go play. Okay?
A-chan's in diapers,
but just look at how bold she is!
Need a hand?
Don't you dare film me.
Not a single shot!
But...
There's nothing I can do about us being here,
but don't come anywhere near me on this trip!
Seems like she really hates you.
Oh, I know. Why don't you film them for now?
I'll put some on you, too, Onii-chan!
Thanks.
Here. Rub, rub...
I always drop my ice cream 'cause I eat so slowly!
Here.
Ah! I love you, Onii-chan!
I love you, too!
I want a kiss too!
Excuse me?
Marie's foot is dirty.
Would you kindly clean it?
I'll give you permission to touch me.
After all, you're special.
You're not going to swim?
I'm happy enough just watching everybody else play.
My sister Kosame.
I am somewhat troubled.
You need to pee?
Your help is appreciated.
I need to go too!
Me too!
Oh no!
I'm gonna go!
Please help, Onii-chan!
Carry me, my brother!
I can sense a reassuring aura when you carry me.
Right, Ninetails?
That was quite close.
Um...
About that thing earlier...
I'll forgive you if you take a photo of the train on the way home!
Wh-What are you staring at?
You look beautiful in that school swimsuit.
What?!
Y-You think that's a compliment? You idiot!
But... thanks.
Sorry! I was sleeping and-
Your hands are quite rough.
Sorry.
Here-we-go!
Leave it to-
Leave it to me!
There!
I won't let you!
I've got-
Boing!
Are you all right, Onii-chan?
Leave it to Yuuna!
Pain, pain, go away!
That's no fair, Yuuna!
I will offer these lips to my dearest brother...
C'mon! Next round!
Here!
Do it, Onii-chan!
Yeah!
Not a chance!
Tsurara, we're starting to drift far away.
Don't worry, Yuki. This is nothing.
That surprised me!
Hold onto me.
It's okay. It's okay.
No way!
Someone... help!
Tsurara, Watayuki!
M-Manservant, I'm glad you're here!
Onii-chan!
Help us, please!
Yuki can't swim!
You'll be okay, Yuki; Manservant is here.
Mizore!
Sorry for the wait.
It's no good. The current's too strong!
Mizore!
Grab hold of the rope!
Amazing, Brother!
I'm stunned!
You're so awesome, Onii-chan!
That was so cool, Mizore!
Uh-um...
Good job, man.
Stop, Hikaru!
Men
Oh, hey there.
Women
You didn't know? This is a family bath, and we've got it all to ourselves.
Don't be shy. Come on in.
No, but-
It's fine. We're family.
Aren't you tired from filming and dealing with Tsurara?
Oh, Rikka, don't touch me in strange places!
I'm so jealous of you. They're so big.
Bath
Will I be that big someday?
I'm sure you will.
I think you have the potential.
You too, Hotaru.
Recently, my bra's been a little...
Should I go on a diet?
Wow! I got sunburnt!
Check out this tanline!
I can't believe I got so tanned in one day!
Rikka's younger than me, yet still...
Are genetics my only hope?
It's wonderful that all of us can get in this large bath, isn't... it...
M-M-M-Manservant!
Tsurara, are you out there?
I'm so excited!
Don't rush. Be careful.
No!
I refuse to let you see!
Wow! It's huge!
Oh? You're here, too, Hikaru.
Y-Yeah.
Wh-What?
What are you doing?
I'm exercising!
Yep, exercising!
Get. Over. There.
You're so weird, Tsurara.
Oh you know, I haven't been too
active lately, so... I was a little stiff, so...
Begin underwater navigation. Objective: Exit hot springs. Velocity: 15 knots.
Here comes Rikka!
What?! Torpedo attack!
It feels lovely!
What a nice bath.
This bath's so big!
Here I am!
Marie too!
Successive attacks unavoidable!
Here I go again!
Stop that, Rikka. They'll all cop-
Huh?
I touched something...
Oxygen levels are too low!
Begin surfacing now.
You pervert!
Wait, that's dangerous!
Stop!
Lech!
Creep!
Calm down, you two-
You all right?
Is he breathing?
Okay, okay. You peed, right?
Baby Princess for Adults!
Baby Princess
for Adults
I've come to you...
I got sunburnt badly today,
so my back's tingling so much I can't sleep.
Could you please massage this lotion onto my back?
Work's kept me so busy lately. Could you do me too?
Don't say that you're busy.
I want to be with you through the night, my prince.
Idiot!
Miharu?!
Sorry about that.
I just had the impulse to tease my cute little brother.
See ya!
Good night, my prince!
Miharu?
Yeah?
It's hot.
Glare.
Ta-da!
In summer, girls just have to wear miniskirts
and show some skin!
Right?
I'm sorry. I wanted you to see the costume that I made.
So Onii-chan, am I super cute?
Stunning?
I'm a bad girl.
I wanted to have you for myself.
I'm a bad girl... aren't I?
What were you doing with Miharu?
The snow falls softly today,
yet you're not coming here
I'm a grown up girl, too.
I'll show you that I'm not a little girl anymore.
What are you guys doing so late at night?!
You're being noisy!
Get back to your rooms!
Five seconds till Tsurara explodes!
Got a minute?
Um...
I know. You don't have to explain anything.
I saw it all
because I was looking for you.
I didn't thank you for saving me earlier.
Th-Thanks.
Yeah.
Don't you have a fever?!
Your face is all red.
Don't stare at me like that.
Now I can't stop staring...
What've we got here? What a scoop.
Mizore!
No, this is-
You were trying to kiss him, weren't you?
Oh, come on.
As if.
Should I try then?
Stop it!
I said nothing happened!
L-Later, Manservant!
It's so fun to tease Tsurara.
Don't you agree?
Hold still.
I don't mind at all if it's you.
Well, this is less significant than space dust.
Hey, what're you-
That's my line.
Oh... well, I was...
I was looking for my bikini!
I'll help you look.
It's fine! I was about to go back because it's getting late.
Why don't you-
What's wrong?!
That's...
What're you doing?!
Let me do this.
Stop!
You're doing too much!
I'm completely fine!
Don't touch me there!
Not the back of my knees-
Don't move around!
Hey!
Stop...
Don't tease me, please.
This is too embarrassing.
It's miraculous that, of the countless people in the world, you became part of our family.
I think you're doing a good job.
Everyone is treating you as part of the family.
Of course, so do I.
Let's start the premiere of the finished promotion video!
Isn't this lovely?
Come on. Hurry up and change, guys!
What the hell?!
Oh dear.
Why is there a video of us changing?
You're so bold!
This is way too embarrassing!
Oh, I get it!
It's a prank, right?
Is this really okay?
Hidden cam?
It's a little weird.
The angle is unusual.
Marie's in the video.
How lecherous, Brother!
Where's Sakura?
Sora's naked!
Is Nijiko cute?
I knew it. Men suck!
How could you, Manservant?!
Wha- Stop! That's dangerous!
You can just die!
You took this, A-chan?
Ippai takusan moromoro zentai
Lots, tons, everything, all of it
Junjou sasetai yamamori cho-dai
I want pure love, give me a bunch
Ippai takusan moromoro zentai
Lots, tons, everything, all of it
Aijou agemasu moratte cho-dai
I'll give you love, please take it
Yudan wa dame kidoccha dame
Don't underestimate it, don't get cocky
Kimi ni wa riyuu shabecchau
I'll tell you why
Tomodachi jya nakute uyamuya ijou rabu kibou
I don't want to be a friend, I want clear love
Kono saki dame sawaccha dame
Don't go any further, don't touch there
Kimi nimo mahou kakacchae
I'll cast a spell on you
Arittake no denshi on kokoro piko piku pika
All the electronic sounds, my heart goes beep, spark, flash
Myu-to wa nashi de koi wo shimashou
Let's turn "mute" off and love each other
Watashi wo narashiteyo
Make me make sounds
A-a, setsunai yabou no forute
Oh, a heartbreaking, ambitious forte!
Konna ni oozei to nakayoku shitemo
Even if I befriend all these people
Hitori ga ki ni naru kimi dake miteru
I'm interested in only one; I see only you
Konna ni oozei no naka no watashi
I'm in this huge crowd
Ki ni shite kurenai kimi wa hidoiyo
So you don't notice me... you're mean
Yume de au dake jya tsumaran
Meeting in a dream is no fun
Atsuku atsuku na-re
Get hotter and hotter!
He's having trouble because he suddenly joined a large family,
so be nice to him during the trip.
So maybe... you could kiss him?
Wasn't everyone trying to give you a kiss?
Mom said that?
I didn't have a clue.
That was... um... I really didn't know!
Bine?